let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who is The Joker's girlfriend?",
        answer: "Harley Quinn",
        options: [
            "Talia Al Ghul",
            "Harley Quinn",
            "Poison Ivy",
            "Hardley Davidson",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which detective is Batman's allie?",
        answer: "James Gordon",
        options: [
            "Harvey Bullock",
            "Sarah Essen",
            "Renne Montoya",
            "James Gordon",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is The Riddler's real name?",
        answer: "Edward Nigma",
        options: [
            "Edward Nigma",
            "Edward Neema",
            "Eddie Nickle",
            "Edward Nemo",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "There have been many Robins but which one is Batman's son?",
        answer: "Damian",
        options: [
            "Jason",
            "Dick",
            "Damian",
            "Tim",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the name of Gothams prison for the crinimally insane?",
        answer: "Arkham Asylum",
        options: [
            "Gotham City Prison",
            "Arkham Asylum",
            "Blackgate Penitentiary",
            "Gotham Supermax",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How did Pamela Isley gain her powers to become Poison Ivy?",
        answer: "Injected with plant-based poison",
        options: [
            "Bit by a venus flytrap",
            "Tricked into a human genome experiment",
            "Injected with plant-based poison",
            "Merged with plant DNA in a lab accident",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What are the names of Batman's parents?",
        answer: "Thomas and Martha Wayne",
        options: [
            "Thomas and Maggie Wayne",
            "Thomas and Martha Wayne",
            "Timothy and Martha Wayne",
            "Toby and Mildred Wayne",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Oswald Chesterfield Cobblepot is the real name of which Batman villian?",
        answer: "The Penguin",
        options: [
            "Mr. Freeze",
            "Deathstroke",
            "Mad Hatter",
            "The Penguin",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What are the Batman villains Harley Quinn, Catwoman, and Poison Ivy collectively known as?",
        answer: "Gotham City Sirens",
        options: [
            "DC Sisterhood",
            "The Trinity",
            "Gotham City Sirens",
            "Birds of Prey",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What former District Attorney became the villain known as Two-Face?",
        answer: "Harvey Dent",
        options: [
            "Floyd Lawton",
            "Harvey Dent",
            "Jason Blood",
            "Todd Evans",
        ]
    },
]